freejobalert.guru 2017-12-02

# Privacy Policy

DISCLAIMER: Any piece of content on this website don't infringe legal rights or laws of any Governmental/Private/NGO firm. Our sole purpose is to provide more user friendly information to the end user of our website that helps him to find the right job. There could be some inadvertent errors in the website but we try out best to avoid those. We cannot be held responsible for such errors, however if you find any errors or wrong information on our web portal, please write it to us we will change it ASAP.

Our first priority is to respect and protect the privacy of our users and we don't share any names, e-mails or any user information to third parties or to anyone. At www.freejobalert.guru, we respect the privacy of the users of our website. Please read below more details about our privacy policy :-

1\. We may collect personal information. The purpose of collecting such information is to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement and/or activities within our website and, if required, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. We will not share our users’ personal information and usage information, except with their consent, with third parties.

2\. We use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users so that we can offer and provide optimized and personalized services to them. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user’s browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user’s computer hard drive.

3\. We will never automatically send your information/offers you do not want.

4\. freejobalert.guru reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website.

Log Files Like many other Web sites, this site makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons This site does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Third-party Advertising We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)
